罗斯吻了我
Ross kissed me.
天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
难以置信吧
It was unbelievable!
天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
现在全部从实招来
Ok, all right. We want to hear everything.
摩妮卡  拔掉电话线  拿酒来
Monica, get the wine and unplug the phone.
瑞秋  结局是好是坏
Rachel, does this end well or do we need to get tissues?
结局非常好
It ended very well.
等我来再讲  等我来再讲
Do not start without me! Do not start without me!
先说那个吻
Okay. All right. Let's hear about the kiss.
是轻拂过你嘴唇的轻吻呢
Was it like a soft brush against your lips...
还是欲火焚身的那种吻呢
...or was it like a "I gotta have you now" kind of thing?
刚开始很炽热  然后...
Well, at first it was really intense, you know? And then....
天啊  然后我们就完全沉醉了
Oh, God. And then we just sort of sunk into it.
他抱着你吗  还是手搭在你的背上
So was he holding you? Or were his hands on your back?
不  开始时他的手搂着我的腰
No, actually, first they started out on my waist...
然后往上滑  最后摸到了我的头发
and then, they slid up, and then, they were in my hair.
然后
And...
然后我吻了她
and then I kissed her.
舌吻吗
Tongue?
-对  -不错
- Yeah. - Cool.
各位  瞧瞧这个坏小子
All right, check out this bad boy!
12兆缓存  500兆的硬盘
Twelve megabytes of RAM, 500-megabyte hard drive...
还有内置电子制表功能
... built-in spreadsheet capabilities...
外加传输速度超过28Kbps的调制解调器
...and a modem that transmits at over 28,000 BPS.
你要用它来干什么
What will you use it for?
玩游戏之类的
Games and stuff.
根本没有工作  没有适合我的工作
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
等一下  这边有一个
Oh, wait, here's one.
你愿意裸体做菜吗
Uh, would you be willing to cook naked?
有招聘裸体厨师的广告
There's an ad for a naked chef?
没  但你如果肯裸体做菜  那或许会愿意裸体跳舞
No, but if you'll cook naked, then you might be willing to dance naked.
然后...
And then....
昨晚亲热得怎么样了
So how'd you make out last night?
真搞笑  让人痛苦的搞笑
That is funny. That is painfully funny.
不  等等
No, wait, wait.
对  只是痛苦而已
Yeah, that's just painful.
等等  我还以为昨天晚上很棒
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great.
没错  是很棒  但是当我回到家
Yeah, it was. But I get home...
我看到朱莉已经把盐水放在我的床头柜上
...and I see Julie's saline solution on my night table...
我就想"老天啊  我到底在做什么"
...and I think, "My God! What am I doing?"
我跟朱莉这么好的女人在一起
Here I am with Julie, this incredible, great woman...
我们互相关怀
...who I care about and who cares about me...
而我就那样抛弃一切吗
...and I'm just throwing all that away?
一杯盐水激发了你那么多感慨
You got all that from saline solution?
我们现在是在谈瑞秋  你跟瑞秋
We are talking about Rachel here. You and Rachel.
我大概有十年时间都在想跟瑞秋的事
Believe me, I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for like ten years now.
但现在我跟朱莉在一起
But now I'm with Julie.
就好像我跟朱莉  我跟瑞秋
So it's like, me and Julie, me and Rachel.
我跟朱莉  我跟瑞秋
Me and Julie, me and Rach...
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel.
-好啊  -你好吗
- Hey, you. - How are you?
-很好  你呢  -很好
- Good. How are you? - Good.
-亲爱的  -朱莉 你好  朱莉
- Hi, honey. - Hi, Julie. Hi, Julie?
朱莉
Julie!
你好吗
How are you?
很好
Good.
大家都在
So everybody's here.
大家都很好
Everybody's good.
你不是要弹什么吗  菲比
So, were you gonna play something, Phoebe?
-其实我...  -快弹
- Well, actually - Play it!
好
All right.
-我不知道你戴隐形眼镜  -什么
- Julie, I didn't know you wore lenses. - What?
好
Okay. Hi.
你们好  好
Hello. Hi. Okay.
那...
So...
这是一首我乱编的
This is a song about a love triangle...
讲述三角恋的歌
... between three people that I made up.
叫做"昨晚其中两个接吻了"
It's called "Two of Them Kissed Last Night."
有个女孩  我们叫她贝蒂
There was a girl We'll call her Betty
有个男孩  咱们叫他尼尔
And a guy Let's call him Neil
我再三强调这一点
Now I can't stress this point too strongly
这故事不是真的
This story isn't real
现在尼尔必须决定  如何取舍
Now our Neil must decide Who will be the girl that he casts aside
是那个他真心相爱的贝蒂
Will Betty be the one who he loves truly
还是我们称为露莉的女孩
Or will it be the one who we'll call Loolie
他必须决定  他必须决定
He must decide He must decide
虽然他纯属虚构  他必须决定
Even though I made him up He must decide
你的简历很漂亮
Well, this is a nice resume.
漂亮  漂亮  漂亮
Nice, nice, nice.
非常不错
Muy impressivo.
拉斯塔特先生  这份工作具体干什么  广告很含糊
Mr. Rastatter, what does this job entail? The ad wasn't clear.
麻克力
Macholate.
-什么  -麻克力
- I'm sorry? - Macholate.
一种完全人工的巧克力替代品
It's a synthetic chocolate substitute.
别客气  试一块
Go ahead, try a piece.
对  我们认为麻克力比巧克力更好吃
Yeah. We think Macholate is even better than chocolate.
好
All right.
很有嚼劲
I love how it crumbles.
-巧克力就没这嚼劲  -是的  小姐
- You see, chocolate doesn't do that. - No, ma'am.
反正呢  我们"很快"会通过食品药物管理局的检验
Well, anyhoo, we should be getting our FDA approval any day now.
希望能够赶得上感恩节
Hopefully, in time for Thanksgiving.
照我们看来呢
See, the way we look at it,
巧克力已经占据了大多需要准备食物的节日
chocolate dominates your major food-preparation holidays.
复活节  圣诞节  等等
Easter, Christmas, what have you.
可我们在想  只要行销搞好了
But, we're thinking, given the right marketing,
我们就能让感恩节成为麻克力节
...we can make Thanksgiving the Macholate holiday.
你不吞下去吗
Aren't you gonna swallow that?
我在等它不冒泡了
Just waiting for it to stop bubbling.
是不是很棒
Isn't that great?
总之
Well, anyhow...
我们在找些厨师来弄新的感恩节食谱
...we're looking for chefs who can create Thanksgiving recipes.
你有兴趣吗
You think you might be interested?
绝对
Abso-...
有
... -lutely!
我爱写食谱  我爱感恩节  而现在呢
I love creating recipes, I love Thanksgiving, and now...
我爱麻克力
... I love Macholate.
真的
Really?
特别是那种余味  简直...
Especially that aftertaste. I tell you...
可以保留到圣诞节
...that'll last you till Christmas.
麻克力慕斯怎么样
How about Macholate mousse?
没什么
It's not...
感恩节的味道
it's not very Thanksgiving-y.
那感恩节清教徒慕斯呢
How about Pilgrim Macholate mousse?
哪里像清教徒
What makes it Pilgrim?
放点搭扣上去
We'll put buckles on it.
罗斯来电话没
Did Ross call?
很遗憾  没有
No, I'm sorry.
他为什么没打来
Why didn't he call?
他要跟朱莉在一起  是不是
He's gonna stay with Julie, isn't he?
他要跟她在一起  然后她会这样
He's gonna stay with her and she's going to be all,
"我是朱莉  罗斯选我"
"Hi, I'm Julie. Ross picked me.
"我们要结婚  生一堆孩子  然后全家一起挖骨头"
We'll get married and have lots of kids and dig up stuff together!"
恕我冒犯  这不是她的风格
No offense, but that sounds nothing like her.
我不知道该怎么办  这简直是一场恶梦
I don't know what to do. What am I gonna do? This is like a complete nightmare!
我知道  一定很难受  "糟糕  两个女人都爱我"
I know. This must be so hard. "Oh, no! Two women love me!
两个都是性感尤物
They're both gorgeous and sexy.
我的钱太多  皮包装不下
My wallet's too small for my fifties,
我的钻石鞋太紧了
...and my diamond shoes are too tight!"
-我有个办法  罗斯  -别碰我的电脑
- Here's a thought, Ross.  - Don't touch the computer.
永远都别碰
Don't ever touch the computer.
罗斯  听着  我送你五个字
Ross, listen. I got two words for you:
三人行
Threesome.
我们用理性来分析  好吗  我们来列个单子
Let's get logical about this. We'll make a list.
"瑞秋和朱莉  优缺点"
"Rachel and Julie: Pros and Cons."
名字用不同字体加粗
We'll put their names in bold, with different fonts,
然后每一栏可以用不同的颜色
...and I can use different colors for each column.
用笔写不行吗
Can't we use a pen?
不行  原始人
No, Amish boy.
我们就先从缺点开始  那比较好玩
Let's start with the cons because they're more fun.
先列瑞秋
Rachel first.
我不知道
I don't know.
我是说
I mean....
好吧  可以说她有时有点娇生惯养
All right, I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
可以这么说
You could say that.
有时候她有点像傻大姐
I guess, sometimes she's a little ditzy, you know?
我觉得她有点太注重她的外表
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
朱莉跟我有很多共同点
And Julie and I have a lot in common...
因为我们都是古生物学家
... because we're both paleontologists, right?
但是瑞秋她只是个女招待
But Rachel's just a waitress.
女招待
Waitress.
好了  你们要玩《毁灭战士》吗
Got it. You guys want to play Doom?
我们也可以继续
Or we could keep doing this.
还有呢
What else?
我不知道
I don't know.
她的脚踝有点胖
Oh! Her ankles are a little chubby.
好  换朱莉了
Okay, let's do Julie.
她有什么不好的
What's wrong with her?
她不是瑞秋
She's not Rachel.
这是麻克力饼屑陷南瓜派
This is pumpkin pie with a Macholate cookie crumb crust.
这个是麻克力红莓蛋糕  这些是麻克力碎屑饼干
This is Macholate cranberry cake, and these are Macholate-chip cookies.
跟印第安人的一样
Just like the lndians served.
天啊
Oh, my God!
太好吃了吗
"Oh, my God" good?
天啊  我不敢相信你给我吃这个
Oh, my God! I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
我的天啊  这一定是万恶之味
Sweet Lord! This is what evil must taste like!
我说这个机器打印不出来
I'm telling you this thing won't print.
对  那个按钮我按了一百次了
Yes, I pressed that button like 100 times.
对热线而言  你没有那么热
For a hotline, you're not so hot.
背景声是什么
What is that in the background?
你在看《星际迷航》吗
Are you watching Star Trek?
你怎么跟朱莉说的  伤她心了吗
Hey, so how'd it go with Julie? Did you, did you break her heart?
是啊  好可怕  她哭我也哭
Yes, it was horrible.  She cried, I cried.
她丢东西打到了我
She threw things, they hit me.
我这么做是对的
I did the right thing.
史巴克真的拥抱了他爸爸吗
So Spock actually hugs his father?
你们有没有...
Hey, do you guys have...
你去哪里了
Where you going?
我刚...
I just got back...
从朱莉家回来
...from Julie's.
不
No, no.
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
是别的事
It's the other thing.
什么是别的事  我怎么想的
Well, what's the other thing? What do I think?
他跟朱莉分手了
He broke up with Julie!
还等什么  快去抱她
Well, go hug her, for God's sakes!
真的
Really?
Really.
我爱的一直是你  瑞秋
It's always been you, Rach.
天啊
Oh, God.
真好
Oh, this is good.
-真是太好了  -我知道
- This is really good. - I know. I know.
几乎
It's almost....
我们出去走走怎么样  就我们两个人
What do you say we go take a walk? Just us. Not them.
-好  我去拿外套  -好  不
- Let me get my coat. - Okay. No, hey!
我帮你拿
I'll get your coat.
他去帮我拿外套  他去帮我拿外套  乔伊
He's going to get my coat. He's going to get my coat, Joey!
我真不敢相信  太难以置信了
I can't believe this! This is unbelievable!
-那是什么  -什么  没什么
- What's that? - What? Nothing!
-我看到我的名字  是什么  -不  不  你看
- I saw my name. What is it? - No, no, see? See?
在打印
It's printing!
那是什么  给我看看
What is it?Let me see!
有人订外套吗
Hey, someone order a coat?
罗斯  钱德勒在电脑上写了关于我的事
Ross, Chandler wrote something about me on his computer
还不让我看
and he won't let me see.
他不给?  他不给!
He won't? He won't!
因为那不是...
Because isn't that...
你正在写的短篇故事吗
...the short story you were writing?
对  是我正在写的短篇故事
Yes, it is a short story that I was writing.
里面有我  那让我看看
And I'm in it? Let me read it.
不行
No!
-快点  -干脆你念给她听好了
- Come on! - Hey, why don't you read it to her?
好吧
All right.
"那是一年夏天"
"It was summer.
"天气很热"
And it was hot.
"瑞秋在那里"
Rachel was there.
"寂寞的灰沙发"
A lonely gray couch.
"奈德大叫  '看啊'"
'Oh, look!' cried Ned.
"然后他就是永远的国王了  剧终"
And the kingdom was his forever. The end!"
就这样  你只写了这些  你真是世上最烂的作家
That's it? That's all you wrote? You're the worst writer in the whole world.
好了  我不再觉得好玩了
This isn't funny anymore.
那张纸上写了我的事情  我要看
There's something about me on that paper, and I want to see it.
不  不可以
No, you don't.
好吧  你们要这么孩子气的话  没关系
You know what, fine. If you guys want to be children about this, that's fine.
我根本就不需要看
I do not need to see it!
这是什么
What is this?
-那是...  -不
- That is....  - No.
罗斯  这是什么
Ross, what is this?
-谢谢  -祝你好运
- Thank you. - Good luck.
你只要记得我多么疯狂地爱你
Okay. Just remember how crazy I am about you, okay?
"有点像傻大姐"
"Kind of ditzy"?
"太注重外表"
"Too into her looks"?
"娇生惯养"
"Spoiled"?
是有点娇生惯养  他应该加上"有点"才对
Now that's a little spoiled.  He was supposed to type "little," the idiot!
"只是个女招待"
"Just a waitress"?
那是...
Now that was....
我是说  相对于...
I mean, as opposed to....
你念完了没有  瑞秋
Okay, is this over yet? Rach?
我的脚踝一点都不胖
I do not have chubby ankles!
不  瑞秋
No! I
好  你看另一边  你看看朱莉那一栏
Okay, look at the other side. Look at Julie's column.
"她不是瑞琪"
"She's not Rachem"?
瑞琪是什么东西啊
What the hell's a Rachem?
那是什么因为我是女招待
Is that a stupid paleontology word I wouldn't know,
而不懂的愚蠢古生物学用语吗
because I'm just a waitress?
不  瑞秋  别这样
No, Rach, come on. Rach! Rach, no, no!
是"她不是瑞秋"
It's "She's not Rachel"!
她不是...
She's not....
瑞秋
Ra--Rachel?
我的日记  太聪明了
My diary! My diary, that's brilliant.
我应该说那是我的日记  她绝不会逼我念我的日记
If I'd said it was my diary, she wouldn't have made me read my diary.
那倒是真的  你很适合在出事的第二天放马后炮
That's true. You'd be a great person to have around after an emergency.
真不敢相信罗斯列了单子
I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
-我知道  -简直浑蛋
- I know. - What a dinkus!
放他一马吧  那是钱德勒的主意
Hey, cut him some slack. It was Chandler's idea.
什么
What?
很好  我正希望你提呢
Oh, good. I was hoping that would come up.
这是你的主意
This was your idea?
拜托  你们想一下  事出必有因
Let's get some perspective here. These things happen for a reason.
对  就是你
Yeah. You!
菲比  帮我一下好吗  你相信因果报应那套狗屁吧
Pheebs, back me up,OK? You believe in that karma crap, don't you?
对  祝你下辈子当大便虫好运
By the way, good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
瑞秋
Rach!
开门好吗
Hey! Open up! Please?
当别人不开门让你进来的时候  那表示"走开"
When somebody does not buzz you in, Ross, that means, "Go away."
那并不表示请你爬防火梯上来
It doesn't mean, "Climb up the fire escape."
我只想念一点你的优点给你听
I just wanna read something. It's your pro list.
我不感兴趣
Not interested.
第一  你看游戏节目时哭的样子
"Number one: the way you cry at game shows.
第二  你对朋友的感情
Number two: how much you love your friends.
第三  你紧张时玩头发的样子
Number three: the way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
第四  重新开始新生活的勇敢
Number four: how brave you are for starting your life over.
第五  你很会逗小本
Number five: how great you are with Ben.
第六  你的香味
Number six: the way you smell."
罗斯  你在干什么
Hey, Ross! What are you doin'?
乔伊  帮我开窗好不好
Hey, Joey. You wanna open the window?
好呀  来
Oh, yeah.
-你在外面干什么 -我...
- What are you doing out there? - I'm....
天啊  你一定冻坏了  知道你需要什么吗
You must be freezing. You know what you need?
来杯热腾腾的麻克力怎么样
How about a nice, steaming cup of hot Macholate?
阿秋  快开门
Rach, come on, open up.
阿秋  别这样  你再给我一次机会
Rach, come on, come on,. You gotta give me another chance.
不
No.
-不  -不就是不
- No? - That's what I said.
也许我们该回避
Maybe we should go.
不  你们真的不用走  我们已经谈完了
No, you guys, you really don't have to go, we're done talking.
拜托  我知道你一定...
Rach, come on, look, I know how you must feel.
不  你不  罗斯
No! You don't, Ross.
想像一下  你觉得自己最大的缺陷
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
如果这个世界上  你最信任的人
Now, how would you feel if the one person that you trusted the most in the world
不止也看成是缺陷
... not only thinks them too...
还用来当做不跟你在一起的理由  换了你会怎么样
... but actually uses them as reasons not to be with you.
就算是那样  我还是想要跟你在一起
No, but see, I want to be with you in spite of all those things.
你真是宽宏大量  罗斯
Oh, well, that's, that's mighty big of you, Ross.
我说了  别走
I said, don't go!
你知道吗
You know what?
如果今天是你列单子
If it were the other way around, there is nothing you could put on a list...
不管你在单子上写什么  都阻止不了我跟你在一起
that would ever make me not want to be with you.
我想这就是我们的不同之处
Well, then I guess that's the difference between us.
我绝对不会去列单子
See, I'd never make a list.
每次遇上这种情况  我都不知道要等多久才能开口
I never know how long to wait in this situation before you can talk again.
我再等一会儿好了
Maybe a little longer.
我其中的一些食谱用的麻克力份量或许有点不寻常
Now, in some of these recipes, the quantities may seem just a little unusual,
像这个椰子麻克力干果棒
Like these coconut Macholate holiday nut bars?
我上面写了四杯椰子  四杯碎干果
I've indicated four cups of coconut and four cups of crushed nut,
而只有一大匙的麻克力
...and only one tablespoon of Macholate.
-不重要了  -什么
- Doesn't matter. - What?
食品药物管理局没有通过
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
实验室老鼠的问题吧
Something about laboratory rats.
天啊  真遗撼
Gosh, I'm sorry.
是呀
Yeah.
总之呢  这是给你的支票
Anyhow, here's your check.
谢谢你出了这么多力
Thank you for all the trouble you went through.
你做的时候没有吃很多吧
Listen, you didn't eat a lot of it while you were cooking, did you?
我吃了一些
Well, I ate some.
一些  那还好  一些可以  一些不是很多
Oh, some is fine. Some is not a lot.
那你尿尿的时候  没有灼痛的感觉吧
So it doesn't burn when you pee, does it?
喂
Hello?
又是他吗
Is that him again?
告诉他我想去接电话  可是我脚踝太胖走不动
Tell him I'd come to the phone, but my ankles are weighing me down.
听着  现在还不是时候
Listen. I don't think this is the best time.
帮我个忙好吗
Look, can you do something for me?
好  什么事
Sure. What?
好的
All right.
来点音乐
Music?
好
Sure.
下一首是罗斯要点给瑞秋的歌曲
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
瑞秋  他要你知道  他为他的行为深感抱歉
Rachel, he wants you to know he's deeply sorry for what he did
希望你能从心底原谅他
and he hopes you can find it in your heart to forgive him.
*看到你眼若冰霜*
*See the stones set in your eyes*
*看到你浑身带刺*
*See the thorn twist in your side*
*我会等你*
*I'll wait for you*
*上天真爱作弄人*
*Sleight of hand and twist of fate*
*她就让我苦苦地等*
*On a bed of nails she makes me wait*
*不论你是否在身旁  我会等你*
*And I'll wait without you*
我们刚接到瑞秋的电话  她说了罗斯做的事
We've just gotten a call from Rachel and she told us what Ross did.
真令人发指  罗斯  如果你在听
It's pretty appalling. And, Ross, if you're listening...
我不想再放你点的歌了
...I don't want to play your song anymore.
我们何不将时间留给还有机会的情侣
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
艾佛  米雪很抱歉用她的车撞你
Avery, Michelle's sorry she hit you with her car...
她希望你们能够解决问题
...and she hopes you two will work it out.
*我有个房间*
*There's a room where*
*可以去*
*I can go*
*倾吐心中的秘密*
*And tell my secrets to*
*在我房里*
*In my room*
谢谢你再度光临
Thanks for coming in again.
不客气  我既没道德  又需要钱
Not at all. I have no morals, and I need the cash.
我们真是一模一样啊
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
这个东西叫做开心鱼
Anyway, they're called Fish-tachios.
味道是跟开心果一样
They taste exactly like pistachios...
但主要是用鱼肉重新压制的
... but they're made of reconstituted fish bits.
来  试试看
Here, try one.
-好  -你没对什么过敏吧
- All right. - You're not allergic to anything?
猫毛
Cat hair.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.